A Guide to the Records of the Division of Outreach and International Affairs, Sahel Regional Financial Management Project, 1982-1986
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the Division of Outreach and International Affairs, Sahel Regional Financial Management Project, 1982-1986
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 35/1/1c
35 Cubic Feet; 25 boxes
This collection consists of the records of the Sahel Regional Financial Management Project that was organized to improve the financial management of Sahelian institutions that manage funds from the U.S. Agency for International Development. The collection includes correspondence, telefaxes, reports, evaluations, financial and legal records, and more. The countries involved were the United States, Senegal, Gambia, Chad, Burkina Fasa, Mali, and Niger.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The collection was transferred to Special Collections in May 1990.
Administrative History
The Sahel Regional Financial Management Project was organized to improve the financial management of Sahelian institutions that manage funds from the U.S. Agency for International Development. The countries involved were the United States, Senegal, Gambia, Chad, Burkina Fasa, Mali, and Niger. The Sahel is the ecoclimatic and biogeographic zone of transition, in Africa, between the Sahara desert to the north and the Sudanian Savanna to the south.
The Sahel Regional Financial Management Project began in the Office of International Programs, established in 1975. It is the predecessor to the Division of Outreach and International Affairs, which was established in 2003.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the records of the Sahel Regional Financial Management Project that was organized to improve the financial management of Sahelian institutions that manage funds from the U.S. Agency for International Development. The collection includes correspondence, telefaxes, reports, evaluations, financial and legal records, and more. It is divided by country and material types.
Arrangement
The collection is in original order, primarily by country and material type.
Index Terms
Subjects:
University Archives; University History
Organizations:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Contents List
- General
  - Country Files - Maps (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Country Files - General (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Project Paper (PP) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Project Paper (PP) Supplement (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agency for International Development (AID) PP Amendment Proposal (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AID Agreement (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AID Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AID "Guidance for Country Development Strategy Statement" (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AID Policy Consumable Shipments (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AID Policy Emergency Leave (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AID Policy Per Diem (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AID Policy Pouch (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AID Policy Travel for Dependents (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Development Project Management Center (DPMC) Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence - Sahel Regional Financial Management Project (SRFMP) Reorganization, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence - Office of International Cooperation and Development (OICD) - Mattox-Hoofnagle (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) Micro Transmissions from OICD/TAD (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - General USDA Micro Transmissions to OICD/TAD (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Possible Candidates for Latter Part of Phase II (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Request for Proposals (RFP) - Phase II (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General Project Extension and Phase II (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University (VPISU) Proposal Internal Approval (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Proposed Subcontract between VPISU and Garrett, Sullivan (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Contractor Employee Biographical Data Sheets (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Educational Background and Resumes (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Technical Proposal, 1986-01-31 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Technical Proposal, 1986-01-31 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - SRFMP; Working Draft - Accounting Manual for a Double Entry Accounting System (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Gambia Contractors (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Niamey Department Development II (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Installation of Minimum Account Ability Standards (draft) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Project Advances and Disallowed Items (draft memo) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Note Introductive Aux Procedures Usaid (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Financiere des Projects (Mali - USAID) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Government Memorandum (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Inistere du Developpement Rural (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sahel Project Certification (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Adequacy of Host Government Accounting Systems (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Government of the Gambia (Report) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Telegrams from the Amembassy Banjul (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - David M. Wilson Correspondence to Monsieur le Ministre (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Speech by H. E. Parker Borg (U.S. Ambassador to the Republic of Mali, 1982-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Project Accounting Systems (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from the Embassy of the U.S. (to the Gambia and Mali) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Niamey, Niger Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - SRFMP Country Team Leader (CTL) Orientation (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The SRFMP Assessment Process and Workshop (Overview) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Personnel/Orientation Front Royal Workshop Evaluation (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Personnel/Orientation Financial Management Team Leaders (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - DPMC Sahel Project (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers, 1982, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Development Communication Report (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Overseas Tour, 1982-08 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Project Implementation Order/Participants (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Code - Congressional and Administrative News, 1981-08 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Country Reports (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Country Reports (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - SRFMP Basic Reference and Background Documents (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - SRFMP Reference Handbook (Volume 1) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - SRFMP Related Papers (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - USDA International Technical Assistance Activities, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - PASA, 1982-09-01 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Project Authorization Niger (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Government Memorandum, 1981-06-05 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - SRFMP Reference Handbook (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Audit of Host Country Accounting, 1981-01-29 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "Promising Approaches to Project Management Improvement" (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - CTL Orientation (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Appendices Documents (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Upper Volta Project Accounting System (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Upper Volta Project Accounting System for Health Planning Project (Box 3, Folder 2.)
  - Upper Volta Project Implementation (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - African Accounting Council (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sahel Regional Financial Management Project Report (03/31/1985) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Country Files - General Pre-Project Materials (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Country Files - Reports Sahel Development Program: Country Strategy Statement (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Country Files - Reports - Report to the Congress - US Development Assistance to the Sahel (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Country Files - Reports - Annual Budget Submission FY 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports Safgrad Project (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports E and F Problems in Host Country Accounting for Utilization of AID Fund in the Sahel (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports E and F Improvements to the Sahel Development Program (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports - Financial Management Problems in Developing Countries Reduce the Impact of Development Assistance (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports - Entente Fund (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports - Open Audit Recommendations (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports - Certification Maintenance (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Country Files - Audit Reports - Agriculture Credit Program (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Small City Management Information System (SCMIS) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - General - Consultant Management Environment (CME) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - SRFMP Reorganization (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Report on Interim Evaluation of SRFMP (Mali and Senagal) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Audit Draft (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - PASA Amendment #3, 1985-10-01-1986-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Voucher Approval: How well does it work?, 1982-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Action-Training in Project Planning and Management (Government of Jamaica), 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Improvements Needed in Management of AID/W Projects (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Systeme Comptable de Base (Manuel de L'Utilisateur) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - SRFMP Project Paper, 1982-08-20 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Accounting Vouchers, 1986-06 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Revue Internationale de la Verification des Comptes Publics (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Standardization Regulations (Gov. Civilians, Foreign Areas) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Reorder Packet #655 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Security Forms (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Executive Project Review (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - General SRFMP Brochure (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Training Possible Seminars by VPI Faculty (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - General V.T. Information - Misc. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Project Cost Estimate, 1982-12-06 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Financial Documents, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Financial Summary, 1985-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Expenditure Report/Transaction Log, 1985-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Transaction Logs/Expenditure Report, 1985-02 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Financial Summary, 1985-02 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Financial Summary, 1985-03 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Expenditure Report, 1985-03 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Financial Documents, 1985-03 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Transaction Logs, 1985-04 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Financial Summary, 1985-04 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Expenditure Report, 1985-04 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Financial Documents, 1985-04 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Transaction Logs, 1985-05 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Financial Summary, 1985-05 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Expenditure Report, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Transaction Logs, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Financial Documents, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Financial Reports, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Accruals, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Transaction Logs, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Financial Reports, 1985-09-30 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Reports of Fund Balances, 1985-06 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Transaction Logs, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Financial Documents, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - AID Project Audi Summary, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Project Proposal Approval Notice (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - VT/VA Object Codes (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Project Budgets (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Contacted Personnel/Agencies for Financial Management (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - List of Project Resources (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Mali Personnel Notes, 1985-04-01 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - SRFMP Financial Reports, 1984-08-1985-03 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - SRFMP/VPI Expenditure Printouts, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - SRFMP/VPI Expenditure Printouts, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Niger Regional Meeting Documents, 1983-10-16-1983-10-28 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Senegal Regional Working Meeting Evaluation, 1984-06-04-1984-06-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Senegal Regional Working Meeting, 1984-06-04-1984-06-08 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Senegal Regional Working Meeting (Duplicates), 1984-06-04-1984-06-08 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Niger Regional Meeting Evaluations, 1984-01-25 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SRFMP Goal and Purpose (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - SRFMP Senior Management Group (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SRFMP Handouts (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Requests for Information, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Tech Plan of Work, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Reports, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Reports, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Reports, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Action Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Action Plan, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Action Plan, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Trip Reports, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Trip Reports, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Trip Reports, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Trip Reports, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Niger - SRFMP; Regional Conference Papers (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Harold Walker; SRFMP Conference Papers (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Harold Walker; Work Plan (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Harold Walker; Conference Papers on Training (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Personnel; Country Team Members - Garman, E. Thomas (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Personnel; Sahelian Experts (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Personnel; Financial Information (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Personnel; Travel and Overseas Information (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Personnel; Policies and Procedures (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Audit, 1981-08-10 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Audit to Congress, 1983-04 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Audit to Congress, 1984-03 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Audit Mali, 1982-09-20 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Category Outlines (Finance, Administration) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SFMIP Follow-up Forms (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - AID Project Guidelines (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SRFMP Material - Taken Out (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - MAMC Programme, 1985-01-07-1985-03-20 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Certification on Audit Recommendations, 1981-09-30 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Overseas Manual - Mali (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - General and Country Sections from Mali Overseas Manual (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Salary and Allowance Policies (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - SRFMP; Draft Work Plan (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - WARDA; Accounting Procedures Manual (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - WARDA; Administrative and Financial Rules (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - PASA, 1984-08-14 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Plans for SRFMP (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - AID Predeparture Orientation, 1982-12 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Reorganization of OICD (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Photos (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1985-07-1985-08 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1985-09-1985-10 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Financial Documents, 1985-12-31 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1985-12-31 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Financial Documents, 1986-01 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Financial Documents, 1986-06-30 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Financial Documents, 1986-08-31 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Financial Report, 1987-01 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - General Team Leader Documents (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - AID/DIHF Development Information System, 1984-08-31 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to Harold Walker (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - USAID Documents; Various Countries (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - AID Country Development Strategy Statement - Senegal, 1983-02 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - AID Project Data Sheet (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - VT Proposed Work Plan, 1985-07-01-1986-06-30 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - SRFMP Quarterly Activity Report, 1985-07-15 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Annual Faculty Report, 1985-01-10 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Burkina Faso and Chad
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Basic Specs for Automating the Accounting and Financial Reporting System of the University of Ouagadougou and USAID Projects in Burkina Faso (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Burkina Faso Double-Entry Accounting Manual (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Manual for Accounting and Preparation of Financial Reports for USAID Financed Projects in Upper Volta (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Manual for Expanding the Accounting System of USAID Financed Projects in Burkina Faso (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Manuel de comptabilite et de preparation des rapports financiers destine aux projets finances par USAID en Haute Volta, revised version (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Manuel de comptabilite et de preparation des rapports financiers destine aux projets finances par USAID en Haute Volta (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Burkina Faso Reports; Manuel de comptabilite et de preparation des rapports financiers destine aux projets finances par Les Fonds PL 480, Section 206 au Burkina Faso (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Burkina Faso Publications; Projet de production des semences de base fonds de commercialisation manueal de comptabilite (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chad; General Materials and Forms (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Chad; Financial and Personal Records (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chad; Agreements (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Chad; Annual Performance Evaluation (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chad; Cables (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Chad; Correspondence - Incoming (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Chad; Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chad; General Information and Maps (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Chad; Personnel, Libiszowski Orientation (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chad; Telexes - Incoming (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chad; Telexes - Incoming (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chad; Telexes - Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Gambia; Leases (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Gambia; Management Development Institute (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Chad and Gambia
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Ministry of Agriculture - Loel, Samir (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Ministry of Health - Loel, Elian (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Ministry of Plan - Phillip, Samir (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Public Works - Phillip, Hank (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Food, O.N.C. - Les (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Caman Africare - Vegetable Gardening Activity (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chad, Libiszowski Reports on Government Departments; Report on Consultancy with SRFMP Washington (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Chad; Ministry of Finance Needs for Automatic Data Processing Report (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chad - Reports; Project Amendment (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Chad - Reports; Regional Projects, Spring 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Chad - Reports; Trip Reports (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Chad - SRFMP; Personnel (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Chad; Progress Reports (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Chad - SRFMP; Work Plan (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Chad - SRFMP; Budget (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Chad - Reports; Miscellaneous Reports (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Chad; Financial Management Consultancy - Lusby, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Chad; Financial Management Guidelines - Baranson, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Chad - Reports; Financial Management Improvement Advisory Team (FMIAT) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Chad; Libiszowksi's Consultancy Report, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Chad; Workshop at University of Chad, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cape Verde - Reports; Trip Reports (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cape Verde (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cape Verde; Agreements (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cape Verde; Cables (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cape Verde; Correspondence - Incoming (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Cape Verde; General Information and Maps (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Cape Verde - Reports; Annual Budget Submission FY, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cape Verde; Review - Perkins, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Gambia; Background and Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Gambia; Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Gambia; Agreements (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Gambia; Annual Performance Evaluation, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Gambia; Cables (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Gambia; Certification (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Gambia; Consultant Possibilities (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Gambia; Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Gambia; General Information and Maps (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Gambia - Publications; Auditing Professional Development Seminar at the Management Development Institute (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Gambia - Publications; Financial Management Newsletters (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Gambia
  - Gambia; Report, "Identification of Action Training Methodology to be Used" by Ruth Harvis (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Gambia; Lusby's Report, 1984-05-1984-06 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Gambia; Auditing Report by Leo Herbert (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Gambia; Publications, Proposals for the Design of a Training Course for Government Stores Personnel (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gambia; Publications, Prototype Workshop on Responsibilities in Financial Management (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gambia; Publications, Report Workshop on Responsibilities in Financial Management (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gambia; Training Plan in Accounting and Auditing, O'Reilly Plan (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Gambia; Publications, Third In-service Course in Financial Management (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gambia; Publications, Draft Top Management Development Workshop (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gambia; Publications, Workplans (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Gambia; Correspondence - Incoming, 3 Folders (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
  - Gambia; Telexes, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Gambia; Telexes, Incoming (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Gambia; Telexes (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Gambia; Final Report, Garman, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Gambia; Reports, Annual Budget Submission FY84 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Gambia; Reports, Appraisal of an Education Project (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Gambia; Reports, Country Development Strategy Statement, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Gambia; Reports, Trip Reports (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Gambia; Audit Manual, 1984-10 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Gambia; Government Auditing Standards (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Gambia; Government Financial Instructions (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Gambia; SRFMP, Budget (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Gambia; SRFMP, Evaluation (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Gambia; SRFMP, Personnel (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Gambia; SRFMP, Progress Reports (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Gambia; SRFMP, Work Plans (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Gambia; Financial Management Handbook by E. Thomas Garman, 3 Folders, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
- Mali
  - Mali, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Mali - Audit Reports; Internal Control Vulnerability Assessment (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mali; Agreements (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mali; Cables (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mali; Certification (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mali; Correspondence - Incoming, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Mali; Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mali; General Information and Maps (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mali; Health and Medical Information (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mali; Leases (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mali; Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Mali; Telexes (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mali; Project Info. (Miscellaneous) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Mali - Projects; Mali Livestock Section II (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Mali - Reports; Annual Budget Submission FY, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Mali - Reports; Country Development Strategy Statement FY, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Mali - Reports; Improving the Effectiveness of USAID - Funded Technical Assistance to Mali (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Mali - Reports; Trip Reports (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mali - SRFMP; Budget (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - December - Outgoing, 1980-12 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Mali - SRFMP; Evaluation (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Mali - SRFMP; Personnel (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Mali - SRFMP; Progress Reports (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Mali - SRFMP; Work Plans (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Mali - Reports; Workshop on Purchasing and Inventory Control (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Planning and Budget in Development Projects - Workshop, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
- Mauritania
  - Manual for Mauritania (Box 11, Folder 1)